<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Startup on J. P. Soares</title>
    <link>https://jpssoares.github.io/tags/startup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startup on J. P. Soares</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jpssoares.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://jpssoares.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 17:28:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jpssoares.github.io/tags/startup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Rundown 4</title>
      <link>https://jpssoares.github.io/posts/weekly4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 17:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jpssoares.github.io/posts/weekly4/</guid>
      <description>Curated selection Intresting articles Facebook loses users for first time ever, market cap drops by $200 billion Meta’s earnings call revealed bad news buried within bad news. The market did not react kindly to the news. Meta’s stock has taken a massive hit and is currently trading down around 24 percent below yesterday’s close, wiping around $200 billion off its market cap.
https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2022/02/facebook-loses-users-for-first-time-ever-market-cap-drops-by-200b/
Article photo
In the Joe Rogan debate, Spotify is acting like a spectator rather than a player In many ways, what Spotify is grappling with right now is the same thing social media platforms like Facebook and Twitter have had to confront over the last five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Rundown 3</title>
      <link>https://jpssoares.github.io/posts/weekly3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 17:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jpssoares.github.io/posts/weekly3/</guid>
      <description>Curated selection Intresting articles Snap is finally profitable Snapchat has more users than ever. Nearly five years after going public, Snap is finally profitable. The company shared the milestone in its fourth-quarter earnings release, where it reported $23 million in positive net income.
https://www.engadget.com/snap-q4-2021-earnings-230605242.html Why gamers hate crypto, and music fans don’t The very different reactions that two different types of fandoms are having to blockchain-based products — and whether that tells us anything about what average people might actually want out of crypto.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
